The next thing to consider is the type of life vest that you are going to be using.
You want one that will fit snuggly around your chest so it doesn't ride up on you when you're in the water.
It also has to be a PFD 2 Coast Guard Approved life vest.
This one here has a zipper and clips as well.
The clips fit securely in and keep it from riding up on you.
It's available in a variety of colors, it's just a personal preference.
For those of you in salt water, the life vest- you want to rinse it with clean, fresh water.
The salt water is like acid, it will eat right through the fabric.
Again, you want to store this in a dry, shady area, indoors preferably.
This particular life vest is for a child.
It's a smaller vest, but it fastens the same way with the clips.
It's just a little bit easier, they're a little smaller.
It's the same type of thing, PFD 2 Approved.
It's something that needs to be cleaned up a little bit.